#### **CURRICULUM VITAE**

# Songhei Lee

Address: Bergsätravägen 23 181 61 Lidingö Mobile: +46 (0)70 396 72 23



### Job Objective

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science with professional experience from soft / hardware testing and quality assurance. Self-managing and responsible project managers who are challenged by problem solving and clear goal focus. My goal is to develop my knowledge in testing.



### **Educational History**

#### Dankook University, Cheonan, South of Korea

Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science & Engineering

Mar 2005 - Feb 2009

### Work experience & Main responsibilities

LG Electronics Nordic AB, Kista, Sweden (Consultant)

Sep 2018 - Mar 2019

Assistant Product Manager

#### **Product managing**

- Price management
- Market trend research regarding competitors market share
- Sales, promotion programs management
- Contact point between the HQ and other subsidiaries
- Sample product management.

### **Demand planning**

- Analyzing PSI data
- Sales and value forecasting
- Communicating with Key account manager for product demand plan

#### Clonix Co., Ltd., Suwon, South of Korea

Mar 2016 - Mar 2017

Page 1

Assistant manager, Senior QA Specialist

#### Software quality assurance

- Participate in product design reviews to provide input on functional requirements, product designs, or potential problems.
- Plan test schedules or strategies by project scope or delivery dates.
- Document software defects, using a bug tracking system, and report defects to software developers.
- Provide feedback and recommendations to developers on software usability and functionality.
- Testing the compatibility of developed programs with new hardware/platform/OS.

#### **Customer support**

- Answer customer telephone calls regarding existing accounts.
- Trouble-shooting software problem through remote assistance.

Songhei, Lee Mobile: +46 (0)70 396 72 23

E-mail: songhei 831.lee@hotmail.com

#### Samsung Electronic Co., Ltd., Suwon, South of Korea (Consultant)

Oct 2008 - Mar 2016

Assistant manager, QA Specialist

#### **Certification Test - WHQL**

- All of the Samsung Desktop/Laptop/All-In-One/Tablet system and Hardware certificate through the WHQL (Windows Hardware Quality Labs) suite.
- Follow-up and BIOS changing Test.

#### Software & Hardware quality assurance

- Monitor program performance to ensure efficient and problem-free operations.
- Measure hardware performance and search problem to fast booting time (Using benchmark tool).
- Touchscreen performance and accuracy test.
- Experience in testing the Compatibility of Samsung Computer system with the other programs.

#### Runstenen Kronan & Antik AB, Sweden

Jan 2020 - Present

Sales associate

#### Managing the store

- Checkout
- Explane about the souvenirs (in English and Korean)
- Exhibit and clean the shop

#### Kotra Stockholm, Danderyd, Sweden

May 2019 - Jun 2019

Marketing coordinator (Shortterm contract)

#### **Business Events support**

- Sweden South Korea business meeting: support of the event (MOU ceremony), data collection & writing, balance account of the event
- Nor-shipping 2019: Data collection & writing

# **Computer literacy**

Programming language: C, Visual Basic, JAVA, HTML5, CSS3

Operation System: Windows all versions, Windows server 2008, 2012

Software packages: Microsoft WHQL suite, Microsoft ADK suite, Kinds of benchmark tools, Microsoft Office

suite

# **Language skills & Cerfiticates**

Language: Korean (native) / English (business level) / Swedish (intermediate - SVA 1 course) / Japanese

(available reading)

Certificate: ISTQB FL, SCJP5.0, MOS XP Master

# Others

- References and certificates are available upon request.

Songhei, Lee Mobile: +46 (0)70 396 72 23 E-mail: songhei 831.lee@hotmail.com